cruisefashion.co.uk 2017-05-08

# Security and Privacy | Cruise Fashion

We view your customer security as paramount, below is an outline of our security policy but if you have any further queries, please contact our Customer Service team. Any personal information you provide to us and from which you can be identified is stored securely and confidentially and is processed fairly and lawfully in accordance with this privacy policy

We take appropriate technical and organisational measures to protect against unauthorised or unlawful processing of your personal information, including encrypting your information to applicable industry standards.

During your visit to our site we may gather certain personal information that is necessary to set up your account, for the purposes of billing, delivery of your goods and queries. We only keep your information for as long as is necessary to process your order, process any applicable refunds, respond to any complaints/feedback or to provide you with promotional information you have subscribed to.

Ordinarily we do not have access to your financial information which is securely transferred directly to our card processing agents and who process it on our instructions.

We supply your information electronically to our couriers who need your details to deliver your orders

When you register your details with us, you have the option to subscribe to future promotions and special offers. You may unsubscribe from this at any time by emailing our **customer services**

We do not transfer your information outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”) unless you are a user located outside the EEA in which case we may need to transfer your information to deliver your goods, process payment/refunds, or to send you promotional information you have subscribed to.

Our website can recognise past users by using cookies. Cookies personalise your visits to our website to meet your individual preferences. You can disable cookies by adjusting your internet settings. 

This Website contains links to other websites with their own privacy policies, we are not responsible for the privacy policies of these websites.

When you supply your information to us you accept the risks associated with the Internet and will not hold us responsible for any loss of your information unless we have breached our duty of care to you.

If you have any queries regarding our use of your personal information or this privacy policy, you should contact our Data Protection Compliance Officer by writing to Sportsdirect.com, Unit A, Brook Park, Meadow Lane, Shirebrook, Mansfield, Nottinghamshire, NG20 8RY.

## Cookie Policy

This policy explains what cookies are, how we use them and how you can switch them off.

#### **1\. How we use Cookies**

We use a combination of our own cookies and third party cookies to enhance your browsing experience and to enable our site to function efficiently. In particular, we use cookies to:

  * enable you to set up an account, place orders and make payments;
  * remember items you place into your shopping basket;
  * remember items you have been looking at so that you can quickly and easily go back to an item you looked at previously;
  * enhance your shopping experience.

#### **2\. What are Cookies?**

Cookies are small files which are stored on your internet browsing device (e.g computer, tablet or phone). Cookies don't store your personal details such as your credit card details, your name or your date of birth.

#### **3\. What types of Cookies do we use?**

Our site uses session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies operate from the moment you log on to the site until the moment you log off. Once you log off session cookies are deleted. Persistent cookies will not be deleted after each session.

**Strictly Necessary Cookies** are essential to our site, if these are disabled, your experience on our site may be interrupted and you may not be able to use a shopping basket or make payment.

**Performance Cookies** collect anonymous data about visitors. We use the data to improve your future experience and identify issues that our users may be experiencing.

**Functionality Cookies** customise the look and appearance of our site. For example, a functionality cookie will remember your username and language preferences next time you visit.

**Targeting or Advertising Cookies** deliver advertisements which are tailored to your web activity. A targeting cookie tracks what you click on whilst on our site, and may share details of what you click on with other organisations such as advertisers. These cookies can also help us to measure the effectiveness of an advertising campaign.

Third party cookies may be used on our website by approved organisations to provide services on our website.

#### **4\. What happens if I turn off Cookies?**

If you disable or delete cookies you may not be able to shop or access important parts of our site. Further information on cookies, including instructions on how to amend your browser settings to turn off cookies, is available widely online.
